[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the marketing mix made up of?",
    "answers": [
      " Advertising",
      " Product, Price, Place, Promotion ",
      "Branding"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Product, Price, Place, Promotion"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the process of dividing a market into smaller groups of consumers with similar needs and characteristics called?",
    "answers": ["The World Wide Web Consortium", "Segmentation", "Google"],
    "correctAnswer": "Segmentation"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is the term for the unique value that a product or service provides to its customers?",
    "answers": ["Value Proposition", "Advertising", "Product Development"],
    "correctAnswer": "Value Proposition"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the difference between a brand and a product?",
    "answers": [
      " A brand is the identity and reputation of a product or company, while a product is the physical item being sold.",
      "Advertising",
      "Place (Distribution)"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": " A brand is the identity and reputation of a product or company, while a product is the physical item being sold."
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is the process of creating and communicating a brand's identity and reputation called?",
    "answers": ["Digital Marketing", " Content Marketing", "Branding"],
    "correctAnswer": "Branding"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is the term for the process of creating and sending messages to potential customers to encourage them to purchase a product or service?",
    "answers": [
      " Advertising",
      "Content Marketing",
      "Branding",
      "Digital Marketing"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": " Advertising"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the process of designing and delivering a product to meet the needs and desires of a specific group of customers called?",
    "answers": [" Product Development", " Brand Identity", "Segmentation"],
    "correctAnswer": "Product Development"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is the term for the process of setting a price for a product or service?",
    "answers": ["Pricing", "Sales", "Social Listening", "Marketing Metrics"],
    "correctAnswer": "Pricing"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the term for the process of making a product or service available to customers through distribution channels?",
    "answers": [
      "Social Listening",
      "Sales",
      " Place (Distribution)",
      "Brand Identity"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": " Place (Distribution)"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is the process of identifying potential customers and creating strategies to convince them to purchase a product or service called?",
    "answers": ["Brand Identity", "Advertising", "Sales"],
    "correctAnswer": "Sales"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What is the term for the process of building and maintaining relationships with customers to retain their loyalty and repeat business?",
    "answers": [
      "Marketing Metrics",
      "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)",
      "Marketing Campaign"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Customer Relationship Management (CRM)"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is the process of using social media and other online platforms to promote a product or service called?",
    "answers": [
      "Marketing Metrics",
      "Digital Marketing",
      " Brand Identity",
      "Advertising"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Digital Marketing"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is the process of analyzing data to make informed marketing decisions called?",
    "answers": ["Marketing Analytics", "Brand Identity"],
    "correctAnswer": "Marketing Analytics"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What is the process of creating and distributing valuable, relevant, and consistent content to attract and retain a specific audience called?",
    "answers": ["Advertising", "Content Marketing", "Digital Marketing"],
    "correctAnswer": "Content Marketing"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is the process of creating a message that resonates with a specific audience and motivates them to take action called?",
    "answers": ["Brand Identity", "Message Development"],
    "correctAnswer": "Message Development"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is the process of promoting a product or service through endorsements and other forms of paid advertising called?",
    "answers": ["Brand Identity", "Marketing Metrics", " Influencer Marketing"],
    "correctAnswer": " Influencer Marketing"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is the term for the visual elements that represent a brand, such as a logo, color scheme, and typography?",
    "answers": ["Branding", " Brand Identity"],
    "correctAnswer": " Brand Identity"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is the process of monitoring and responding to conversations about a brand on social media and other online platforms called?",
    "answers": ["Branding", "Marketing Analytics", " Social Listening"],
    "correctAnswer": " Social Listening"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What is the term for the process of measuring the effectiveness of marketing strategies and tactics?",
    "answers": ["Marketing Analytics", "Marketing Metrics"],
    "correctAnswer": "Marketing Metrics"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is the process of creating and executing a plan to achieve a specific marketing objective called?",
    "answers": ["Advertising", "Marketing Campaign", "Brand Identity"],
    "correctAnswer": "Marketing Campaign"
  }
]
